<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://llfung.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://llfung.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2026-02-26T17:02:56+00:00</updated><id>https://llfung.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Lloyd Fung&apos;s academic homepage. Still under construction. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my new blog!</title><link href="https://llfung.github.io/blog/2026/Welcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my new blog!"/><published>2026-02-25T12:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2026-02-25T12:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://llfung.github.io/blog/2026/Welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://llfung.github.io/blog/2026/Welcome/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my new blog! This will be a place where I occasionally share some preliminary thoughts and ideas about fluids, ML and everything in between. None of these are peer-reviewed or checked, so take them with a few pinches of salt, but you’ll get to see a lot of my raw ideas before getting butchered by reviewer #2.</p> <p>The reason for writing here instead of publishing a paper is because I simply have way more ideas than I have time to work them into a proper paper. Being a big believer that science is a community effort, I thought it might be better to throw it out to the community and get feedback (i.e., criticisms) than to let the idea die in my notebook. I don’t mind people working on/”borrow” my ideas. All I ask of you is to be civil and acknowledge them if you ever find any of my ideas useful. To be fair, I believe that most of my ideas contain some flaws or misconceptions, so please feel free to point them out in any way you can.</p> <p>I will also use this space to share/promote/show off some of my students’ works, which are definitely superior to most of my dumb ideas.</p> <p>For upcoming few weeks, I will uploading one of the project my brilliant student, Sean De Marco, has been working on last summer. He has been comparing how Neural Networks and Finite Elements represents a PDE solution from a theoretical perspective, drawing parallels between the two. For those who is very into (or despise) Physics-Informed Neural Networks, this is going to be an interesting read!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="misc"/><category term="ideas"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a time for everything - a time to be born and a time to die... so are my ideas]]></summary></entry></feed>